Before love. After sex.
Two Night Stand is a romance, comedy film directed by Max Nichols.
After an extremely regrettable one night stand, two strangers wake up to find themselves
snowed in after sleeping through a blizzard that put all of Manhattan on ice.
They're now trapped together in a tiny apartment, forced to get to know
each other way more than any one night stand should.
Megan, played by Lio Tipton.
Alec, played by Miles Teller.
Faiza, played by Jessica Szohr.
Cedric, played by Kid Cudi.
Bouncer, played by Berto Colon.
Chris, played by Josh Salatin.
Two Night Stand is a 2014 American romantic comedy film directed by Max Nichols, written by Mark Hammer,
and starring Miles Teller, Lio Tipton, Jessica Szohr, Leven Rambin, and Scott Mescudi.
The film was given a limited theatrical release in the United
States on September 26, 2014, by Entertainment One.
The film explores themes of new year's eve, new york city,
snowstorm, one-night stand, relationship.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.